{ 
  "results":[
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 5 U+0078 5 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "A. 25",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 25",
          "B. 10",
          "c. 15"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 5 U+0078 2 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "B. 10",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 25",
          "B. 10",
          "c. 15"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 3 U+0078 5 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "C. 15",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 25",
          "B. 10",
          "c. 15"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 15 U+0078 2 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "B. 30",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 25",
          "B. 30",
          "c. 15"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 8 U+0078 5 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "C. 40",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 25",
          "B. 10",
          "c. 40"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 12 U+0078 5 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "A. 60",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 60",
          "B. 10",
          "c. 15"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 2 U+0078 9 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "A. 18",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 18",
          "B. 20",
          "c. 7"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 25 U+0078 5 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "A. 125",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 125",
          "B. 110",
          "c. 115"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 8 U+0078 8 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "B. 64",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 16",
          "B. 64",
          "c. 15"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 10 U+0078 5 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "C. 50",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 15",
          "B. 10",
          "c. 50"
          ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "What is 2 U+0078 40 =  ",
      "correct_answer": "B. 80",
      "incorrect_answers": [
          "A. 42",
          "B. 80",
          "c. 82"
          ]
    }
  ]
}
          